bargainnews.com 2005-12-10

# Bargain News Privacy Policy

**Bargain News Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers Bargain News's treatment of personally identifiable information that Bargain News collects when you are on the Bargain News site, and when you use Bargain News's services. This policy also covers Bargain News's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Bargain News's business partners share with Bargain News or that Bargain News may collect on a partner's site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Bargain News does not own or control, or to people that Bargain News does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

Bargain News collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Bargain News account, when you use certain Bargain News products or services, when you visit Bargain News pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Bargain News may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. When you register with Bargain News , we ask for your name, email address, zip code,  and personal interests. Once you register with Bargain News and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Bargain News also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Bargain News cookie information and the page you requested. Bargain News uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Bargain News will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Bargain News may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: We have your consent to share the information;  We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Bargain News to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us)

**Cookies**

Bargain News may set and access Bargain News cookies on your computer. Bargain News allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy  policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Bargain News's cookies. Bargain News uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Bargain News products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

Bargain News gives you the ability to edit your Bargain News Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want Bargain News to contact you about specials and new products. You may request deletion of your Bargain News account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Please be advised that some statistical information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Security**

Your Bargain News Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas Bargain News uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Bargain News may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. For questions or comments on this policy e-mail [webmaster@bargainnews.com](mailto:%20webmaster@bargainnews.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Comments) or write Webmaster, Bargain News, L.L.C. 30 Nutmeg Drive Trumbull, CT 06611

Copyright ©1996-2005 Bargain News, LLC  
Software Development and Site Design by NNCO Group  
Privacy Policy    Terms & Conditions   
2
